const combo = [
    {
    "question": "The ability to combine several objects into a new one in Javascript is called",
    "options":["Encapsulation", "Composition", "Inheritance", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Composition",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 1
    },
    {
    "question": "The ability to to call the same method on different objects and each respond in their own way is called",
    "options":["Encapsulation", "Polymorphism", "Inheritance", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "Polymorphism",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 2
    },
    {
    "question": "Variables that act as placeholders for the values that are to be input to a function when it is called is",
    "options":["Placeholders", "Parameters", "Arguments", "All of these"],
    "answer" : "Parameters",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 3
    },
    {
    "question": "What does comparison operators return in Javascript?",
    "options":["String", "Number", "Boolean", "All of these"],
    "answer" : "Boolean",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 4
    },
    {
    "question": "What are two ways to access the properties of an object",
    "options":["Bracket and curly notation", "Curly Notation", "Bracket and dot notation", "All of these"],
    "answer" : "Bracket and curly notation",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 5
    },
    {
    "question": "If var str = wonderful day. What does str.substring(3,7) return",
    "options":["erf", "derf", "nderf", "none of these"],
    "answer" : "derf",
    "points" : 20,
    "key": 6
    },
    {
    "question": "What is the command to display a prompt?",
    "options":["Alert", "Prompt", "Console.log", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "None of these",
    "points" : 20,
    "key": 7
    },
    {
    "question": "What value can confirm() return?",
    "options":["True", "False", "True and False", "None of these"],
    "answer" : "None of these",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 8
    },
    {
    "question": "How do you change string of number to a number?",
    "options":["toNumber()", "toInt()", "parseNum()", "parseInt()"],
    "answer" : "parseInt()",
    "points" : 20,
    "key": 9
    },
    {
    "question": "If a variable is declared within an if/else condition, what is its scope?",
    "options":["Global scope", "Local scope", "Block scope", "All of these"],
    "answer" : "Block scope",
    "points" : 10,
    "key": 10
    }

    

]

export default combo;